[
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "What time signature has 2 minim beats to a bar?",
    "incorrect": [
      "3/2",
      "2/4",
      "5/4"
    ],
    "correct": "2/2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "How can you represent 2/2 with a letter?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Capital T",
      "Capital T with a line through the middle",
      "Capital C"
    ],
    "correct": "Capital C with a line through the middle"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "What time signature can be represented by a capital C with a line through the middle",
    "incorrect": [
      "3/2",
      "2/4",
      "5/4"
    ],
    "correct": "2/2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "What time signature is also known as cut common time?",
    "incorrect": [
      "3/2",
      "2/4",
      "5/4"
    ],
    "correct": "2/2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "How many minim beats are there in cut common time per bar?",
    "incorrect": [
      "4 minims",
      "3 minims",
      "5 minims"
    ],
    "correct": "2 minims"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "What time signature has 3 minim beats to a bar?",
    "incorrect": [
      "2/2",
      "2/4",
      "4/2"
    ],
    "correct": "3/2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "What time signature has 4 minim beats to a bar?",
    "incorrect": [
      "2/2",
      "2/4",
      "3/2"
    ],
    "correct": "4/2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "What time signature has 3 quaver beats to a bar?",
    "incorrect": [
      "2/2",
      "3/4",
      "3/2"
    ],
    "correct": "3/8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "How many minim beats are there in 2/2?",
    "incorrect": [
      "4 minims",
      "3 minims",
      "5 minims"
    ],
    "correct": "2 minims"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "How many minim beats are there in 3/2?",
    "incorrect": [
      "4 minims",
      "2 minims",
      "5 minims"
    ],
    "correct": "3 minims"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "How many minim beats are there in 4/2?",
    "incorrect": [
      "3 minims",
      "2 minims",
      "5 minims"
    ],
    "correct": "4 minims"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "timeSignatures",
    "question": "How many quaver beats are there in 3/8?",
    "incorrect": [
      "2 quavers",
      "8 quavers",
      "4 quavers"
    ],
    "correct": "3 quavers"
  }
]
